Do you like to keep fit?
你喜欢健身吗？
We’re always told that regular exercise is good for our body and mind.
我们总是被告知，定期锻炼有益身心。
More and more people are taking up activities that improve their fitness.
越来越多的人开始参与各类健身活动。
But is there a risk some of us might get obsessed and overdo it?
但有没有这样一种风险，我们中的一些人会因此变得痴迷，甚至运动过量呢？
Well, for some people, fitness has become an obsession as they aim for perfection.
对有些人而言，为了追求完美身材，健身已经变成了一种执念。
And fitness trackers and apps can add to this addiction, especially if someone is driven by achievement and perfectionism.
健身追踪器和相关应用会加剧这种沉迷，尤其是对于那些受成就感和完美主义驱动的人来说。
And sharing data on social media means exercising becomes public and competitive, which could cause problems in someone who is vulnerable.
而在社交媒体上分享运动数据，会让健身变成一件公开且充满竞争性的事，这可能会给身心脆弱的人带来困扰。
Experts say this can lead to a medical condition called orthorexia nervosa, or addiction to ‘healthy’ eating and over-exercise.
专家表示，这种情况可能会引发一种名为健康食品强迫症的疾病，具体表现为沉迷于“健康”饮食和过度运动。
Untreated, it can lead to malnutrition and mental health complications.
如果得不到及时干预，会导致营养不良和心理健康方面的并发症。
According to a BBC Worklife article: “Research from scientists at University College London in 2017 found that higher Instagram usage was associated with increased likelihood of developing orthorexia, especially among followers of the ‘healthy eating’ influencers.”
据英国广播公司职场生活栏目一篇文章称：“伦敦大学学院的科学家在2017年开展的一项研究发现，频繁使用照片墙这类社交平台，会提高人们患上健康食品强迫症的概率，尤其是那些关注健康饮食网红的用户。”
Too much exercise can also take its toll on someone’s physical health as well.
运动过量同样会损害身体健康。
Symptoms of over-exercising include injuries such as stress fractures, tendinitis and a low immune system.
运动过量的症状包括应力性骨折、肌腱炎这类运动损伤，以及免疫力下降。
So how much exercise is too much?
那么，运动多少才算过量呢？
Research by the Journal of the American College of Cardiology found the ideal pace to jog was about eight kilometres per hour – and that it was best to jog no more than three times a week or for 2.5 hours in total, showing that moderate jogging is possibly more beneficial than being inactive or undertaking strenuous jogging.
《美国心脏病学会杂志》的一项研究发现，慢跑的理想速度约为每小时8公里，且每周慢跑次数最好不超过3次，总时长不超过2.5小时。这表明，适度慢跑可能比久坐不动或高强度慢跑更有益。
If you’re more of a couch potato than a sprinter, this might sound like good news.
如果你是个爱宅家的懒人，而非短跑健将，这个研究结果听上去或许是个好消息。
But for amateur athletes who can’t help but push their bodies to the limit, the advice from Martin Turner, a sports and exercise psychologist, is, “it’s all about letting go, not being obsessed, learning not to control everything, saying, ‘You don’t need to be perfect.’”
但对于那些忍不住要把身体逼到极限的业余运动员，运动心理学家马丁·特纳给出的建议是：“关键在于学会释怀，不要过分执念，学着不去控制所有事情，要告诉自己‘你不必事事追求完美’。”